http://www.conveyorservices.com/privacy/

Privacy
One of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors.  This Privacy Policy document contains types of personal information that we collect, record and how we use it.
We collect and process your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and in compliance with General Data Protection Legislation (GDPR 2018).  If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, please contact us.
Consent:
By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.
Personal Information we collect:
The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear at the time we ask you to provide your personal information.
We will never collect any unnecessary personal information from you.
If you contact us directly or register on our website, we may receive some or all of the following information about you: your name, email address, mobile number, telephone number, your preferred method of contact, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide.
We collect Device Information using the following technologies:
Cookies are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org
Log files track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, internet service provider, referring/exit pages and date/time stamps. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.
The purpose of the information is for analysing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movement on the website, and gathering demographic information
Web beacons, tags, and pixels are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the site.
How we use your information:
We use the information we collect in various ways, including to:
Communicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners, including for customer service, in order to provide you with our products and services.
Meet our legal, statutory and contractual obligations.
Provide, operate, and maintain our website.
Improve, personalise, and expand our website.
Understand and analyse how you use our website.
Develop new products, services, features, and functionality.
Send you emails.
Find and prevent fraud.
We do not and will not provide your personal data to any third party for marketing purposes.
Third Party Privacy Policies:
Our website may contain links to other websites.
This Privacy Policy of KP Conveyor Services Ltd does not apply to other advertisers or websites.
We are therefore advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information.
They may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options.
You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options.
To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
GDPR Data Protection Rights:
We would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:
The right to access – You have the right to request copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.
The right to rectification – You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request that we complete the information you believe is incomplete.
The right to erasure – You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.
The right to restrict processing – You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.
The right to object to processing – You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.
The right to data portability – You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.
If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.
Children’s Information:
Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet.
We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.
KP Conveyor Services Ltd does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13.
If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.
Updates to our Privacy Policy:
Our Privacy Policy is regularly reviewed and all updates will be placed on our website. Our Privacy Policy was last updated on 1st July 2020.
====================================================================END
© 2020 Conveyor Services • Privacy
